<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<ModMetaData>
  <name>Kolra's Oni Race Mod (Continued)</name>
  <packageId>Mlie.KolrasOniRaceMod</packageId>
  <author>Kolra Sindri</author>
  <url>https://github.com/emipa606/KolrasOniRaceMod</url>
  <supportedVersions>
    <li>1.0</li>
    <li>1.1</li>
    <li>1.2</li>
    <li>1.3</li>
  </supportedVersions>
  <modDependencies>
    <li>
      <packageId>erdelf.HumanoidAlienRaces</packageId>
      <displayName>Humanoid Alien Races</displayName>
      <steamWorkshopUrl>steam://url/CommunityFilePage/839005762</steamWorkshopUrl>
      <downloadUrl>https://github.com/erdelf/AlienRaces/releases/latest</downloadUrl>
    </li>
    <li>
      <packageId>jecrell.jecstools</packageId>
      <displayName>JecsTools</displayName>
      <steamWorkshopUrl>steam://url/CommunityFilePage/932008009</steamWorkshopUrl>
    </li>
  </modDependencies>
  <loadAfter>
    <li>erdelf.HumanoidAlienRaces</li>
    <li>jecrell.jecstools</li>
  </loadAfter>
  <description>[img]https://i.imgur.com/WAEzk68.png[/img]
Update of Kolra Sindris mod
https://steamcommunity.com/sharedfiles/filedetails/?id=1887026903
with permission

- Added Royaly patch

[img]https://i.imgur.com/7Gzt3Rg.png[/img]

[table]
    [tr]
        [td][url=https://invite.gg/Mlie][img]https://i.imgur.com/zdzzBrc.png[/img][/url][/td]
        [td][url=https://github.com/emipa606/KolrasOniRaceMod][img]https://i.imgur.com/kTkpTOE.png[/img][/url][/td]
    [/tr]
[/table]
	
[img]https://i.imgur.com/NOW7jU1.png[/img]
A race of what some might call demons, or others might call friends. The Reds are known for their ferocity in combat, The Greens for their ability to help make a colony function, And The Blues the colony thinkers. Their home was destroyed, but now it is up to you to try and rebuild.
Now with weapons! art courtesy of Itzal, they are the best!

Somebody asked for what each race was good at so here ya go:
Reds are good at mining, combat, and have a low psychic sensitivity.
Greens are good at farm work, cooking, and social interaction.
Blues are good at intellectual, medical, and construction jobs

Well, this is my first ever proper mod, if you have any suggestions, questions, or bugs to report, please drop a message in the discussions. No this mod is not complete yet, i plan to add apparel, weapons, backstories, items, and all the various goodies in the future, until then this is the finished barebones race. So i do hope you can enjoy!

Also, thank you odz for the horns! and Thank you gloomy for permission to use your hairs in this mod until i can get custom hairs finished!

Note: This should be compatible with oni of the rim, if you get any errors about the two please report the bug in the bug reporting discussion so i can fix it post haste.

WARNING: latest update may break old saves because i had to fix a hediffs giver because onis were not bleeding out

[img]https://i.imgur.com/Rs6T6cr.png[/img]
[list]
[*] See if the the error persists if you just have this mod and its requirements active.
[*] If not, try adding your other mods until it happens again.
[*] Post your error-log using [url=https://steamcommunity.com/workshop/filedetails/?id=818773962]HugsLib[/url] and command Ctrl+F12
[*] For best support, please use the Discord-channel for error-reporting.
[*] Do not report errors by making a discussion-thread, I get no notification of that.
[*] If you have the solution for a problem, please post it to the GitHub repository.
[/list]
</description>
</ModMetaData>
